Yakanpa Idol
The first of the 48 training?
The third?
Retirement
This is me,
I really love music.
Kpop.
I listen to Kpop and Western music, of course, but
Classical music
Yodeling...
Yodeling?
I can't do that.
I enjoy listening to various genres with that kind of hyung.
It's fun.
I see.
We also listen to French music.
Oh, wow! You play like that?
Yes, I do.
I can't sing.
But I love to listen to it.
Is that the original?
No.
It's really just the candy flossies.
Since the taste has changed a bit.
It's changed, hasn't it?
Since the change.
I guess...
English is now used in the lyrics
Ame-Flashee's
Yes, yes, yes.
I have to study English for this.
Then I started to listen to Western music
After listening to western music
I started to like K-POP
I started listening to Korean music
I wondered how the French pronounce it.
I got curious.
Oh my God!
That's why I started listening to it more and more!
That must have made you very happy, Morimichi!
That's right.
Morimichi's very own.
Even yodeled.
Yodel?
I'm sorry, it's inconvenient.
What is that?
Is that a folk song?
Yes.
I don't know much about it.
I think it's a folk song.
Where was it yodeling?
Dirty, dirty, dirty...
Yes, yes, yes...
You know...
I like it.
They're so comfortable.
Unique.
It's like a foreign audition show.
Yes, yes, yes.
I saw a clip of a little girl yodeling on YouTube.
I saw it on YouTube.
That's when I started to like yodeling.
Yodeling is Austrian
Austria.
It's a region within Austria, like the Swiss-German Mile.
Oh, I see.
That's a regional folk song.
It's not really a folk song.
Folk songs sung by the people who work on the farms there.
That's right.
Wait, you can sing this?
I can't sing.
I'm terrible at it.
But if you keep doing this...
Even in auditions...
Yes, sure.
Well, it's not for that.
It's just to get you started.
"Can you yodel? That's what you're getting at, isn't it?
That's right.
I do it at home, even though I suck at it.
Wow.
That's interesting, because there's so much music from all over the world.
That's right.
There are trends, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
I try to listen to music.
I try to listen to it often.
What's the current trend?
What's popular now?
Something from the 70's.
You're going back there now?
I feel like it's going back to the 70's.
It's a little bit Japanese style.
I have the image that pop music with a bit of Japanese style is popular.
It goes back to the 70's.
Or the middle-aged people in the 80s.
And you listen to that kind of music too?
That's right.
And incorporate them into your music?
Yes, sir.
The range of AmeFlash's musicality.
That's right.
We have to change a little bit.
I think we're doing something new.
That's true, you've changed a lot, haven't you?
Yes, we have.
Wow.
What do you mean from there?
Yes.
Well...
No, no, no, no, no. That was interesting.
It was.
Yes, it was.
Yes. Yes.
So, the three elements that make Ira...
Food, dance and music.
Thank you very much.
And now Güllard?
You keep it simple.
I understand.
I'll take that as a yes.
This program...
Kensuke!
Mr. Kebabu
Akki
Mr. Rupi
This program was provided by Nami!
Thank you very much!